Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Moving Images Collection FILMS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Transport Workers Union of America, 1930-1967
  - Transport Workers Union Local 100 mass meeting/rally. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 25:58., Dec 27, 1959; cuid8074 (Item T 18-H 15)
  - (Part of?) Michael Quill press conference announcing a Transport Workers Union contract proposal for the New York City Transit Authority. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 00:43., 1959; cuid8075 (Item T 18-H 16)
  - Mass meeting of the Transport Workers Union during a strike against New York City Transit Authority. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 7:10., 1959; cuid8076 (Item T 18-H 17)
  - (Part of?) press conference called by Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill criticizing New York City Transit Authority for its deal with the Consolidated Edison company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:14., 1959; cuid8077 (Item T 18-H 18)
  - Transport Workers Union announces its opposition to proposed merger of Eastern and American Airlines. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 8:40., 1959; cuid8078 (Item T 18-H 19)
  - Press conference by Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill on wildcat strike by Transport Workers Union bus drivers. New York, NY. Press conference; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:15., 1959-1960; cuid8079 (Item T 18-H 20)
  - Press conference by Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill on wildcat strike by Transport Workers Union bus drivers. New York, NY. Press conference; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 4:32., 1959-1960; cuid8080 (Item T 18-H 21)
  - Tape 19, cuid36995 (Box 29)
    Duration: 59 minutes
  - New York City mayor Robert F. Wagner, Jr., delivers a primary election campaign speech at a meeting of the Transport Workers Union. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 10:00., 1959-1960; cuid8081 (Item T 19-H 22)
  - A labor union (possibly the Furniture Workers' Union) "affair"--a banquet/dance and award ceremonies. Location unknown. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 19:24., 1950-1955; cuid8082 (Item T 19-H 23)
  - Transport Workers Union (municipal transit workers?) picket line; Transport Workers Union leaders address mass rally. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:55., 1950-1959; cuid8083 (Item T 19-H 0)
  - Various press conferences held by Michael Quill and other leaders of the Transport Workers Union; Transport Workers Union rallies and meetings; interview with Senator Wayne Morse. New York, NY; Philadelphia, PA. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 16:55., 1950-1959; cuid8084 (Item T 19-H 1)
  - Press conference by Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill on union's demands to New York City Board of Transportation or New York City Transit Authority. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:40., 1950-1959; cuid8085 (Item T 19-H 2)
  - Michael Quill and other Transport Workers Union officers negotiating with the New York City Transit Authority? Brooklyn, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 3:10., 1961; cuid8086 (Item T 19-H 3)
  - Leaflet distribution; Michael Quill at press conference. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 1:30., 1950-1959; cuid8087 (Item T 19-H 4)
  - Tape 20, cuid1028 (Box 29, Item 20)
    This tape contains T 20-H 5, T 20-H 6, T 20-H 7, T 20-H 8, T 20-H 9, T 20-H 10, T 20-H 11
    Format: BetacamSP, Estimated Duration: 00:45:57, BW
  - Buses and passengers in mid-town Manhattan. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:23., 1950; cuid8088 (Item T 20-H 5)
    A digitized copy of this film is available on tape 20.
  - Santa Claus promotes public transportation. New York, NY? Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 3:04., 1950-1959; cuid8089 (Item T 20-H 6)
  - Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill announces end of a wildcat strike by Philadelphia TWU workers. Philadelphia, PA?. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:20., 1950-1959; cuid8090 (Item T 20-H 7)
  - Statement by Transport Workers Union special counsel Arthur Goldberg on TWU representation of New York City transit workers. New York, NY. Filmed press release; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:35., 1950-1959; cuid8091 (Item T 20-H 8)
  - Transport Workers Union Local 100 party. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 1:30., 1950-1959; cuid8092 (Item T 20-H 9)
  - Trims and outtakes from a number of different films or shoots, including footage from a New York City mayoral campaign film and of a Transport Workers Union demonstration, and shots of New Yorkers' feet. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 29:52., 1950-1959; cuid8093 (Item T 20-H 10)
  - Michael Quill announces that a bus strike has been called off. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 2:05., 1950-1965; cuid8094 (Item T 20-H 11)
  - Tape 21, cuid36996 (Box 29)
  - Mixed trims and outtakes, including shots of street signs in New York City, audiences of Transport Workers Union meetings, TWU leaders addressing meetings, different press conferences held by Michael Quill, pickets against the Pennsylvania Railroad, and an address by Michael Quill to members re: the union. New York, NY; Pennsylvania? Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 25:13., 1950-1969; cuid8095 (Item T 21-H 12)
  - Michael Quill answers questions about a threatened strike against the Pennsylvania and New York Central Railroad. Location unknown. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 6:40., Jan 21, 1960; cuid8096 (Item T 21-H 13)
  - Why Pennsylvania Railroad Strike? Television program that announces calling of a strike by the Transport Workers Union against the Pennsylvania Railroad, and explains genesis of and reasons for the strike. New York, NY? Complete television program; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 14:58., Aug 31, 1960; cuid8097 (Item T 21-H 14)
  - Tape 22, cuid36997 (Box 29)
  - New York City Labor Day parades of 1960 and 1961. New York, NY; Peck and Peck (clothing store), New York, NY; New York Public Library, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 19:48., 1960, 1960; cuid8098 (Item T 22-H 15)
  - Transport Workers Union's strike against the Philadelphia Transit Company. Philadelphia, PA; Town Hall, Philadelphia, PA. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 32:22., 1961; cuid8099 (Item T 22-H 16)
  - Tape 23, cuid36998 (Box 37)
    Duration: 56 minutes
  - Reports To Membership Of Local 234. Television broadcast by the Transport Workers Union to its membership on its new contract with the "PTC" (Philadelphia Transit Company?). Philadelphia, PA. Complete television program; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 30:54., Jan 19, 1961; cuid8100 (Item T 23-H 17)
  - Matthew Guinan and Ellis Van Riper speak at Transport Workers Union joint Executive Committee meeting. New York, NY; Sheraton-Atlantic Hotel, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 23:15., Jun 1961; cuid8101 (Item T 23-H 18)
  - Tape 24, cuid36999 (Box 37)
    Duration: 48 minutes
  - Trims of members speaking from floor at Transport Workers Union meeting; Transport Workers Union officers addressing same meeting off-screen. New York, NY; Sheraton - Atlantic Hotel?, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 23:23., Jun 1961; cuid8102 (Item T 24-H 19)
  - Transport Workers Union meeting where formation of a labor party is discussed and Robert F. Wagner, Jr. is endorsed as candidate for mayor of New York City. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 20:12., Aug 23, 1961; cuid8103 (Item T 24-H 20)
  - Robert F. Wagner, Jr. at Transport Workers Union meeting. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 1:15., Aug 23, 1961; cuid8104 (Item T 24-H 21)
  - Tape 25, cuid37000 (Box 37)
  - Candidates for mayor, comptroller and president of city council in New York City election address meeting of the Transport Workers Union. New York, NY; New Yorker Hotel, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 20:15., Aug 23, 1961; cuid8105 (Item T 25-H 22)
  - Labor Day Parade. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:38., 1961; cuid8106 (Item T 25-H 23)
  - Jimmy Hoffa speaks at Transport Workers Union's 11th Biennial convention. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 3:12., Oct 2, 1961-Oct 6, 1961; cuid8107 (Item T 25-H 0)
  - Years Of Challenge. Documentary report by the Transport Workers Union on its strike against the Pennsylvania Railroad, strikes by TWU locals against the Philadelphia Transit Company and the Brooklyn Union Gas Company, and the union's plans for the years ahead. New York, NY; Manhattan Center, New York, NY; Philadelphia, PA; Altoona, PA; Sheraton-Atlantic Hotel, New York, NY. Complete film; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 24:15., Jan 15, 1961, Sep 1, 1960, Dec 27, 1959; cuid8108 (Item T 25-H 1)
  - Tape 26, cuid37001 (Box 37)
    Duration: 62 minutes
  - Years Of Challenge. Second copy of this documentary with only partial soundtrack, but superior visual quality. New York, NY; New Yorker Hotel, New York, NY. Complete film; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 24:21., 1959-1961; cuid8109 (Item T 26-H 2)
  - Mass meeting of Transport Workers Union; leaders speak. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 6:37., Nov 1961; cuid8110 (Item T 26-H 3)
  - Mass meeting of Transport Workers Union; leaders speak. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 10:35., Nov 1961; cuid8111 (Item T 26-H 4)
  - Mass meeting of Transport Workers Union; leaders speak. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 9:14., Nov 1961; cuid8112 (Item T 26-H 5)
  - Audience at Transport Workers Union meeting. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:42., Nov 1961; cuid8113 (Item T 26-H 6)
  - Audience at Transport Workers Union meeting. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 1:48., Nov 1961; cuid8114 (Item T 26-H 7)
  - Picket signs at meeting of Transport Workers Union. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 1:12., Nov 1961; cuid8115 (Item T 26-H 8)
  - Tape 27, cuid37002 (Box 37)
  - Michael Quill addresses mass meeting of Transport Workers Union. New York, NY; Manhattan Center (auditorium), New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 9:57., Dec 28, 1961; cuid8116 (Item T 27-H 9)
  - Matthew Guinan addresses mass meeting of Transport Workers Union. New York, NY; Manhattan Center (auditorium), New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 8:48., Dec 28, 1961; cuid8117 (Item T 27-H 10)
  - Speakers at Transport Workers Union Brooklyn Union Gas Company strike rally; Brooklyn Union Gas Company strike picket line. New York, NY; Brooklyn, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 4:00., 1961; cuid8118 (Item T 27-H 11)
  - Strike rallies during Transport Workers Union strike against Brooklyn Union Gas Company. Brooklyn, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 7:05., 1961; cuid8119 (Item T 27-H 12)
  - Rally by Transport Workers Union Local 101 against (Brooklyn Union?) Gas Company. Brooklyn, NY; Borough Hall, Brooklyn, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:05., 1961; cuid8120 (Item T 27-H 13)
  - Speakers at Brooklyn Union Gas strike rally in front of Brooklyn Union Gas Company headquarters. Brooklyn, NY; Court Street, Brooklyn, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 11:05., 1961; cuid8121 (Item T 27-H 14)
  - Press conference on Transport Workers Union strike against the Brooklyn Union Gas Company. New York, NY; City Hall, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 8:08., 1961; cuid8122 (Item T 27-H 15)
  - Transport Workers Union officers entering Gracie Mansion (mayor of New York's official residence); Transport Workers Union strikers picket Brooklyn Union Gas Company. New York, NY; Gracie Mansion, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:45., 1961; cuid8123 (Item T 27-H 16)
  - Transport Workers Union official reports on progress of negotiations with Brooklyn Union Gas officials. New York, NY; Gracie Mansion, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:10., 1961; cuid8124 (Item T 27-H 17)
  - Tape 28, cuid37003 (Box 37)
    Duration: 38 minutes
  - Transport Workers Union leaders address TWU mass meeting on subject of attempted corporate takeover of Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY; Manhattan Center (auditorium), New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 14:50., Jun 13, 1961; cuid8125 (Item T 28-H 18)
  - Transport Workers Union leaders address TWU mass meeting on subject of attempted corporate takeover of Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 4:32., 1961-1962; cuid8126 (Item T 28-H 19)
  - Michael Quill addresses Transport Workers Union meeting on attempted corporate takeover of Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 10:05., Jun 13, 1961; cuid8127 (Item T 28-H 20)
  - Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill announcing strike against New York City's private bus lines. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 4:55., Nov 21, 1961; cuid8128 (Item T 28-H 21)
  - Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill announces union's intention to become actively involved in the stockholder struggle over the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Filmed press release; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:05., 1962; cuid8129 (Item T 28-H 22)
  - Tape 29, cuid37004 (Box 37)
  - At a mass meeting, Transport Workers Union leadership presents proposal to membership on how to combat a corporate takeover of the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 28:25., 1961; cuid8130 (Item T 29-H 23)
  - Arbitration hearing(s?) before Theodore Kheel on the insolvency of the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 26:09., 1962; cuid8131 (Item T 29-H 0)
  - Tape 30, cuid37005 (Box 29)
    Duration: 36 minutes
  - Emergency mass meeting called by Transport Workers Union Local 100 to vote on resolution to strike against the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY; St. Nicholas Arena (New York, NY). Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 34:02., Feb 21, 1962; cuid8132 (Item T 30-H 1)
  - Tape 31, cuid37006 (Box 29)
  - Lobbying trip to New York State Legislature by strikers during Transport Workers Union strike against Fifth Avenue Coach Company; Fifth Avenue Coach Company strike victory meeting; TWU participation in New York City St. Patrick's Day parade. Albany, NY; New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 30:35., Mar 4, 1962, Mar 17, 1962, 1962; cuid8133 (Item T 31-H 2)
  - Michael Quill's rebuttal (broadcast on WCBS-TV) to Roy Cohn and Lawrence Weissman's televised statements (broadcast the previous night on the same station) about the Transport Workers Union's strike against the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Complete televised statement; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 14:30., Mar 9, 1962; cuid8134 (Item T 31-H 3)
  - Tape 32, cuid37007 (Box 29)
    Duration: 60 minutes
  - Mass meeting of Transport Workers Union strikers against Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY; Manhattan Center auditorium, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 31:35., Mar 14, 1962; cuid8135 (Item T 32-H 4)
  - Mass meeting of Transport Workers Union strikers against Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY; Manhattan Center auditorium, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 10:31., Mar 14, 1962; cuid8136 (Item T 32-H 5)
  - Transport Workers Union delegation in New York City St. Patrick's Day parade; TWU strike picket line against Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY; St. Patrick's Cathedral, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 3:20., Mar 17, 1962; cuid8137 (Item T 32-H 6)
  - Transport Workers Union's Fifth Avenue Coach Company strikers picket New York Governor Nelson Rockefeller's offices; New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade. New York, NY; 22 West 55th Street, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 11:20., Mar 15, 1962, Mar 17, 1962; cuid8138 (Item T 32-H 7)
  - Tape 33, cuid37008 (Box 29)
    Duration: 64 minutes
  - Picket lines, rallies, meetings during Transport Workers Union strike against the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 9:20., 1962; cuid8139 (Item T 33-H 8)
  - Fifth Avenue Coach Company pensioners in wheelchairs being helped on and off buses by Transport Workers Union members and Transport Workers Union officials. New York, NY; Association of the Bar of the City of New York (headquarters), New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 3:30., Nov 16, 1962; cuid8140 (Item T 33-H 9)
  - Transport Workers Union picket line by pensioners of the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY; 20 Exchange Place, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 10:00., 1962; cuid8141 (Item T 33-H 10)
  - Stockholders' meeting of Fifth Avenue Coach Company; pickets in front of Biltmore Hotel. New York, NY; Biltmore Hotel (New York, NY). Probably dailies; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 13:27., 1962; cuid8142 (Item T 33-H 11)
  - Transport Workers Union pickets at the headquarters of the Fifth Avenue Coach Company. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:32., 1962; cuid8143 (Item T 33-H 12)
  - Transport Workers Union pickets Fifth Avenue Coach Company headquarters. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:40., 1962; cuid8144 (Item T 33-H 13)
  - Matthew Guinan speaks at Transport Workers Union picket line at Fifth Avenue Coach Company headquarters. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:35., 1962; cuid8145 (Item T 33-H 14)
  - Michael Quill announces end of strike by workers on the New York City Omnibus and Third Avenue bus systems. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:12., 1962; cuid8146 (Item T 33-H 15)
  - Victory demonstration by Transport Workers Union strikers against the Fifth Avenue Coach Company; workers in bus repair shop. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 11:30., 1962; cuid8147 (Item T 33-H 16)
  - Tape 34, cuid37009 (Box 29)
  - Signing of 1964/65 contract between Transport Workers Union and the New York City Transit Authority; press conference following the signing; report on this contract to a Transport Workers Union body (joint executive board of Local 100?) by union officers. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 31:14., Jan 28, 1964, Jan 1964-Feb 1964; cuid8153 (Item T 34-H 22)
  - New York City Mayor Robert F. Wagner, Jr. reports to press on his discussions with Transport Workers Union officials, New York City Transit Authority officials and mediators on contract negotiations. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 2:35., 1963; cuid8152 (Item T 34-H 21)
  - Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill discussing breakdown of negotiations with New York Transit Authority and threatened strike. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 10:45., Oct 30, 1963; cuid8151 (Item T 34-H 20)
  - Press conference following statement by Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill proposing nationalization of the nation's railroads. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 7:50., Jun 10, 1963; cuid8150 (Item T 34-H 19)
  - Another take of Transport Workers Union's filmed press release (see Tape #34 – Hour #17, above), with Michael Quill voicing union's opposition to the merger of the Pennsylvania and New York railroads. New York, NY; Sheraton-Atlantic Hotel, New York, NY. Filmed press release; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 1:32., Jan 15, 1962; cuid8149 (Item T 34-H 18)
  - Transport Workers Union filmed press release; Michael Quill voices union's opposition to the merger of the Pennsylvania and New York Central Railroads. New York, NY; Sheraton-Atlantic Hotel, New York, NY. Press release; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 4:15., Jan 15, 1962; cuid8148 (Item T 34-H 17)
  - Tape 35, cuid1029 (Box 29, Item 35)
    This tape contains T 35-H 23, T 35-H 0
    Format: BetacamSP, Estimated Duration: 01:00:00, BW
  - Part 2--Transport Workers Union 30th Anniversary meeting (convention?) New York, NY; Americana Hotel, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 30:10., 1964; cuid8154 (Item T 35-H 23)
    A digitized copy of this film is available on tape 35.
  - Part 1--Transport Workers Union 30th Anniversary meeting (convention?) New York, NY; Americana Hotel, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 28:08., 1964; cuid8155 (Item T 35-H 0)
  - Tape 36, cuid1030 (Box 29, Item 36)
    This tape contains T 36-H 1, T 36-H 2, T 36 H-3, T 36-H 4
    Format: BetacamSP, Estimated Duration: 00:26:00, BW
  - Transport Workers Union's Michael Quill announces signing of contract between union and Pennsylvania Railroad. New York, NY? Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 2:50., 1964; cuid8156 (Item T 36-H 1)
    A digitized copy of this film is available on tape 36.
  - Press conference on contract negotiations between Transport Workers Union and New York City Transit Authority--Michael Quill speaks and unidentified spokesperson for NYCTA speaks. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Sound. Running Time: 10:00., 1964-1965; cuid8157 (Item T 36-H 2)
  - 1966 New York City Transit strike; location shots of San Francisco; gas storage tank. New York, NY; Queens, New York, NY; San Francisco, CA; Golden Gate Bridge, San Francisco, CA; Brooklyn Bridge, New York, NY; Manhattan Bridge, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 7:07., cuid8158 (Item T 36-H 3)
  - Michael Quill's funeral service at St. Patrick's Cathedral. New York, NY; St. Patrick's Cathedral, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 3:25., 1966; cuid8159 (Item T 36-H 4)
  - Tape 37, cuid37010 (Box 29)
  - Pan American Airways airplane repair shops. Location unknown. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 10:25., 1960s; cuid8160 (Item T 37-H 5)
  - Subway tunnels; subway station platforms. Fashion show. New York, NY; 103, 110, 116 Street subway stations, New York, NY. Footage; Color and B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:35., 1960-1969; cuid8161 (Item T 37-H 6)
  - John Quill? (Michael Quill's son) applauding. Location unknown. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 00:25., undated; cuid8162 (Item T 37-H 7)
  - A negotiating session between union officials and management? New York, NY? Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 2:55., undated; cuid8163 (Item T 37-H 8)
  - Sequences and outtakes from documentary United We Are Invincible (A documentary on the Transport Workers Union's 1941 strike against the New York City Omnibus Corporation and Fifth Avenue Coach Company). New York, NY; City Hall, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 13:30., cuid8164 (Item T 37-H 9)
  - Interior shots of a New York City powerhouse facility. New York, NY; Franklin Delano Roosevelt Drive, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 9:45., 1950-1959; cuid8165 (Item T 37-H 10)
  - Trains; train passengers; unemployed workers. Location unknown. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 1:32., 1960-1969; cuid8166 (Item T 37-H 11)
  - Material-- including statements by both union and management--on Transport Workers Union strike against the Pennsylvania Railroad. Philadelphia, PA; Union Station, Washington, D.C.. Footage; B/W; Sound; Silent. Running Time: 13:38., Sep 1960; cuid8167 (Item T 37-H 12)
  - Tape 38, cuid37011 (Box 34)
  - Deserted waterfront, train station, trains, and train yards; Transport Workers Union's participation in 1960 New York City Labor Day Parade. New York, NY; New York Public Library, New York, NY; Hoboken, NJ; Pennsylvania Railroad Station, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 19:35., Sep 1960; cuid8168 (Item T 38-H 13)
  - Exterior shots of a New York City powerhouse facility. New York, NY; Franklin Delano Roosevelt Drive, New York, NY; East River, New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 7:46., 1950-1959; cuid8169 (Item T 38-H 14)
  - Interior shots of a New York City powerhouse facility - mostly its main plant. New York, NY. Footage; B/W; Silent. Running Time: 8:38., 1950-1959; cuid8170 (Item T 38-H 15)